**Last updated:** 16th July 2024

About this Privacy Policy
-------------------------

At Wakelet, the privacy of you and your students is very important to us.

We do not sell any personal information to advertisers or third parties.

We only share data with third parties when necessary to provide and improve the service - never for advertising or to monetize that data.

As stated in our terms and conditions, Wakelet does use your personal information for certain stated purposes, such as providing and improving the service and communicating with Registered Users (but not anonymous users).

Our Privacy Policy below describes what information we collect from you, how we use that information, and the legal basis we have to process your information.

This Privacy Policy governs how Wakelet Limited (“we” or “us”) a limited company incorporated under the laws of England and Wales with company number 07483296 and with its registered office and main trading address at Wakelet, Bright Building, Manchester Science Park, Pencroft Way, Manchester M15 6GZ, United Kingdom uses and shares personal information collected by our website at Wakelet.com, the Wakelet mobile app, and any associated services and content (the “Service”). We are the data controller in respect of any information we collect about you on or through Wakelet.

This policy only applies to us and to our Agents and how we will use your personal information. Please be aware that once personal information has been posted on Wakelet this will be visible to the public (unless you tell us that you do not want it to be publicly available) and we cannot control what other Wakelet users do with any information you share on or through Wakelet. Be careful with your own information and what you are willing to share.

The Definitions at the end of this Policy set out the meaning of any capitalised words used in this Policy.

1\. Wakelet is a Curation and Collaboration Platform
----------------------------------------------------

Wakelet is for both public and private use. Whenever you add Content through Wakelet that is not created as a private display it will be public, and when you provide us with User Content or make User Comments on a non-private collection it is published so that anyone can view it.

For users signed up to the Wakelet Individual and Wakelet Individual Pro plans, Content published and shared publicly is accessible to everyone, including search engines, and you may lose any privacy rights you might have regarding that Content. In addition, information shared publicly may be copied and shared throughout the Internet, including through features native to Wakelet Services, such as commenting and embedding.

If you are a teacher or parent who is using Wakelet with or for children under the age of 13, then you should ensure that children are registered onto an Education or Education Pro plan, and that you have selected the privacy controls available to you. If we become aware that children are posting content on Wakelet that is publicly accessible, then we can require verifiable parent or teacher consent as a condition to continue public access or, in the absence of such consent, convert the postings to private use.

2\. Information Wakelet Collects and how it is used
---------------------------------------------------

Wakelet may collect personal information from Registered Users as described below.

### 2.1 Registered User Account Information

When a Registered User creates an account on the Service, we ask you to provide your email address and password, or to authenticate yourself through a third-party service, like Google or Microsoft single sign on. When you authenticate through another site, that account is linked to your Wakelet account. Once linked, we may collect and store personally identifying information that you have provided to that third-party service, and consented to having shared with services like us (please see section 4.2). Information gathered includes your name, email address, avatar, and public data.

We will store the email address and password that you provided to create your Wakelet Account and any information you or we add to your Wakelet account, including your name, handle, bio, profile image and any links you choose to add to your Wakelet account. Where you use a third-party site to authenticate your Wakelet account, we do not receive or store passwords for your linked accounts.

Occasionally, we might need to use your email address to send you important information about our Services. We might need to send you some administrative information, tell you something important about your account or changes to our Services, or update you on new policies or terms. These administrative communications are considered part of our Services and your Wakelet account.

### 2.2 Third Party Site Information

When you link your Wakelet account to a third-party service account, we may receive your biographical information (birthday, education and similar information particular to you) or your geographic location from that third-party service (if you have provided that information to the service and made it available for Wakelet to access).

We may store and use this information to improve and personalise Wakelet and make suggestions to you about Content and Users that may be of interest to you.

You should take care when linking with a third-party service account that you have checked (using that service's settings) that you are comfortable with the information that they will share with us. As a general practice, we strongly urge you to make careful judgements about any personal information you disclose to Internet services, including Wakelet and any third-party services you link to us.

### 2.3 Communications with Us

If you contact us, or we contact you, with any query or comment about Wakelet or your use of Wakelet, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

### 2.4 Surveys and Market Research

We may ask you to complete surveys in connection with your Wakelet Account where we may receive your name, email address, account use information and opinions. We use this personal information for research purposes. We anonymise the data and answered questions so that it is no longer personal information and use this for our own purposes.

### 2.5 Technical Information

We may also keep details of your visits to Wakelet including, but not limited to:

* Traffic data
    
* Location data
    
* Web logs and other communication data
    
* The resources that you access when you use Wakelet

We automatically receive and record information from your web browser when you interact with Wakelet. This information may include:

* Browser type and version
    
* Operating system and version
    
* Language preference
    
* Website or service that referred you to Wakelet
    
* Date and time of each web request you make
    
* Screen display information
    
* Information from any cookies we have placed on your web browser

We may collect information about your device, including, where available, your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration.

We use this information to fight spam, malware and identity theft. We may also use it to create a profile of your use of Wakelet, to personalise Wakelet for you, and to generate aggregate, non-identifying information about how people use Wakelet.

We also collect your IP address when you navigate to a third-party website, which has established a Wakelet frame on its website. We use your IP address only for the purpose of displaying the relevant collection to you.

### 2.6 Information relating to User Content

In some cases, we may collect information by analysing your User Content. We may do this where you upload a link to Wakelet, by analysing the content of any such link and determining its broad subject matter (for example, sports, music, technology, science etc.) This allows us to improve our Services by enhancing your ability to organise content, search topics of interest, and generally provide additional features and functionality.

### 2.7 Information Relating to Your Use of Wakelet

We collect information about how you use Wakelet, whether you are a Registered User or User. This includes general usage information such as:

* The number and frequency of visits
    
* The pages or features of Wakelet people have visited
    
* The links on Wakelet they have clicked on
    
* The length of visits
    
* The Users you have followed
    
* The collections you have liked
    
* The comments you make
    
* The Users you interact with

Some of this information may be associated with the IP address used to access Wakelet and some may be associated with your Wakelet account, such as the topics you search for and the help pages that you visit.

We will use this information to help improve the Service. We will also use this information to identify Content that you are likely to be interested in or to suggest Content and Users that we think may be of interest to you (both on Wakelet and by email).

### 2.8 Location Information

In some cases, we collect and store information about where you are located by converting your IP address into a rough geolocation. We may use location information to improve and personalise the Service for you by finding and presenting Content to you that we think will be of interest to you based on your location, for example news stories or topics of interest similar to those you post.

### 2.9 Information Collected through Email Tracking

To measure the deliverability and interest of our emails for Registered Users, we may embed information, such as a web beacon or tag, in them. This allows us to see which of our emails you have read and clicked-through from so that we can analyse the effectiveness of our communications and seek to make them more relevant for you in the future.

### 2.10 Cookies and Similar Technologies

Wakelet uses cookies (small text files placed on your device's hard disk) and similar technologies to provide the Service, to better understand how you interact with Wakelet, to monitor aggregate usage by our Users and Registered Users and web traffic routing on Wakelet, and to customise and improve Wakelet. Our cookies, both session cookies and persistent cookies, do not, by themselves, contain information that personally identifies you.

Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser - by changing its settings - to stop accepting cookies, or to prompt you before accepting cookies from the websites you visit. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies), you may not be able to access all or parts of Wakelet. Unless you have adjusted your browser settings so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon as you visit Wakelet.

3\. Information We Share
------------------------

Wakelet does not sell User personal information.

We never share information we receive from you unless:

* We have your permission to share that information
    
* We have given you prior notice that the information will be shared, and with whom
    
* That information is aggregate information or other information that does not identify you

### 3.1 Third-Party Services

This Privacy Policy only covers information we collect, it does not cover information collected by other services. If you access or otherwise share information with third-party services through Wakelet Services, you are responsible for reading and understanding those other services' privacy policies (and we recommend you do this before sharing the information).

You can access third-party services through Wakelet, for example, Users can embed externally-pointing links in their content and Users can click on those links to reach other sites and services. We also allow Users to share information that you provide to us or embed a collection into a third-party site, like posts and comments, with other services, for example, Users may share posts on Twitter and Facebook.

In some circumstances, we might share your stored information, such as IP addresses, with our third-party service providers for the purposes of operating and improving Wakelet Services.

Those third-party services might include:

* Our help desk and technical service providers
    
* Our email and website hosts
    
* Our professional advisors (lawyers, accountants, surveyors, tax advisors etc.)
    
* Third-party widgets (embedded tweets, embedded Facebook posts, Google login etc.)

When we share information under those circumstances, we have appropriate contractual protections in place. Unless we tell you differently, our service providers will not have any right to use personal information, or any other information we share with them, beyond the scope and duration of what is necessary to assist us. We may share or disclose non-private information, aggregate information, or other non-personal information with people and entities with which we are doing business.

We may also share User personal information for legal, protection, and safety purposes. For example:

* We may share information to comply with applicable laws
    
* We may share information to respond to lawful requests and legal processes
    
* We may disclose or transfer your personal information in connection with the sale, merger, bankruptcy, sale of assets or reorganization, in whole or in part, of our company provided we send you advance notice at least 5 days prior to such event
    
* We may share information in an emergency, such as protecting the safety of our employees and agents, our Users, or any person

Wakelet reserves the right to share Users' personal information to respond to duly authorized information requests of governmental authorities or where required by law. Wakelet reserves the right to use or disclose personal information provided to Wakelet in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements or if Wakelet reasonably believes that use of disclosure is necessary to protect Wakelet's rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. We also reserve the right to use or disclose personal information provided to Wakelet to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, including exchanging information with other companies and organisations for fraud protection and the prevention of spam and malware.

### 3.2 Third Party Widgets

Our Services include a wide variety of widgets and social media features, such as Social Login Buttons (e.g. Facebook, Google), Embeds (e.g. Tweets, Instagram posts), and Search Integrations (e.g. YouTube API Services, further information available at YouTube [Terms of Service](https://www.youtube.com/t/terms), [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy), [API Client Terms of Use and Privacy Policies](https://developers.google.com/youtube/terms/developer-policies#a.-api-client-terms-of-use-and-privacy-policies) and [Google Security Setting](https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions)). These typically involve including a Software Development Kit (SDK) or iFrame from the third-party site. These widgets collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on the Service, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Your interactions with these features are governed by the Privacy Policy of the company providing it.

#### Use of Google Workspace APIs:

Wakelet does not use data obtained through Google Workspace APIs to develop, improve, or train generalized AI or machine learning models.

### 3.3 Service Providers

We share data with the following service providers:

| Service Provider | Details |
| --- | --- |
| AWS Cloud Services | holds our main data store and hosts our Website. |
| DotDigital | holds email subscriptions, including email addresses and summarised public Wakelet information. |
| Google Analytics | holds aggregated user data for monitoring site usage, in order to enable us to continue improving the Services based on trends observed in behaviours. |
| Google Cloud | customer identity and access management (CIAM) platform to help manage and protect user accounts. Provides email and document hosting which may contain PII (e.g. as a result of support requests). Also provides access to AI models for classifying and understanding content. |
| Hotjar | is used to observe anonymized users interacting with Wakelet pages and features in order to understand pain points and make improvements. |
| Hubspot | CRM platform, used to house contact information for Wakelet users, community members, inbound contacts from marketing activity, and support tickets. No student data is stored in our CRM. |
| Microsoft Azure | uploaded images are scanned for inappropriate content and filtered appropriately. Also provides access to various AI models for content understanding. |
| OpenAI | provides access to AI models for various use cases. Receives (but does not store or train on) content in order to provide better suggestions and results. |
| Pinecone | stores public content in a format suitable for searching. |
| Slack | is used for team messaging and may include information necessary to handle support requests. Any content older than 30 days is automatically removed. |
| User Flow | provides on-site prompts and tours for onboarding, to highlight changes and new features and events/webinars that users may wish to attend. |

The School/District understands that Wakelet will rely on one or more subcontractors to perform services under this Agreement. Wakelet has shared the names of these subcontractors within our Privacy Policy. All subcontractors and successor entities of Wakelet will be subject to the terms of this Agreement. Wakelet ensures on an annual basis that the data collection and privacy practices of their third parties are in alignment with Wakelet's.

Additionally, Wakelet's policy is that all Data in its possession and in the possession of any subcontractors, or agents to which Wakelet may have transferred Data, are destroyed or transferred to the School/District under the direction of the School/District when the Data are no longer needed for their specified purpose, at the request of the School/District.

4\. The Purposes for our use of your information
------------------------------------------------

We collect, use and share the data that we have in the ways described above:

* As necessary to fulfil our Rules and Terms of Service
    
* To provide the Service, including updating, securing, troubleshooting and providing support
    
* To improve, develop and personalise the Service
    
* To send the User information including confirmations, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages
    
* To identify specific Users in our system
    
* To comply with applicable laws, including website accessibility laws that may require transcription of audio or other methods to make User content available on the Service

5\. Information Security
------------------------

All information provided to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or you have chosen) a password to access certain parts of Wakelet, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential and not sharing it with anyone. It’s important for you to prevent unauthorized access to your account and personal information by choosing and protecting a strong third-party service password and by limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished using Wakelet. We will never email you to ask for your password or other Account Information; if you receive such an email, send it to us so that we can investigate and take any appropriate action.

We have put appropriate security measures in place to prevent your personal information from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to only those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know. They will only process your personal information under our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.

While we use reasonable efforts to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected data breach and will notify you, and any applicable regulator, of a breach where we are legally required to do so.

If Wakelet becomes aware of a systems security breach by an unauthorized party or that any user data was used for an unauthorized purpose, we will comply with relevant state and other data breach laws. We will notify users of any breach resulting in unauthorized release of data electronically within 72 hours, at minimum, and without unreasonable delay so that you can take appropriate steps. The notification will include: date of the breach, the types of information that were subject to the breach, general description of what occurred, and steps Wakelet is taking to address the breach.

### 5.1 Where We Store Your Personal Data

Some of our service providers are based outside of the European Economic Area so their processing of your personal data will involve a transfer of data outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”).

Where we transfer your personal information outside of the EEA, we ensure a similar degree of protection is given to it by ensuring at least one of the following safeguards is implemented:

* We will only transfer your personal information to countries that have been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection for personal information by the European Commission
    
* We may use specific contracts approved by the European Commission that give personal information the same protection it has in Europe
    
* Where we use providers based in the US, we may transfer information to them if they have agreed to the Standard Contractual Clauses (SCC) for data transfers between EU and non-EU countries which requires them to provide similar protection to personal data shared between Europe and the US

For US-based schools and districts who subscribe to one of our Education plans and share data via rostering services such as Clever or Classlink, PII and district data is stored in the US.

6\. Data Retention
------------------

We store the information we collect only for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting or reporting requirements.

We store the information we collect from Registered Users for as long as you have an Account and for 14 days thereafter. After this time, it will be purged from our data store and caches. Logs may contain some user information and are retained for up to 30 days. The incremental back-up system of the AWS Dynamo data store can roll back tables over a time period of up to 35 days. Therefore, data is completely erased after 49 days. Anonymous aggregated analytic data is held in Google Analytics indefinitely.

We store the information we collect from Users (without a Wakelet account) for 30 days, until logs are cleared. Anonymous aggregated analytic data is held in Google Analytics indefinitely.

We periodically cleanse all information stored and will delete your IP address 30 days after collection.

For users who are a part of a school or district paid plan (Education or Education Pro) as part of their institution, we provide the opportunity for them to transfer their account to a personal account to take with them should they leave the school or district (for example a student who has built a digital portfolio on Wakelet), with the permission of their school or district. To authorise and provide instructions on the handover of accounts, please email [support@wakelet.com](mailto:support@wakelet.com) and a member of the team will assist. If permission for transfer of their data is not granted, Wakelet will follow the instructions of the school or district on termination of their contract.

Users undertaking a free trial will be given an option at the end of that trial to upgrade to retain their content generated during the trial, or end the trial and return to their free account. At the end of the free trial period if the user does not upgrade, all data generated in the trial will be deleted.

7\. GDPR
--------

Under the General Data Protection Regulation, you have the right to access, rectify, port and erase your data.

You also have the right to:

* Request access to your personal information and receive a copy of the personal information we hold about you to check we are processing this lawfully
    
* Request that the personal information we hold about you is corrected or updated
    
* Request that personal information we hold about you is erased. You can exercise this right where we have no good reason for continuing to process your personal data (subject to any legal reasons for needing to continue holding the personal data)
    
* Object to our processing of your personal data where we are relying on a legitimate interest or are processing for direct marketing purposes
    
* Restrict our processing of your personal data
    
* Request the transfer of your personal data to you or a third party in a structured, commonly-used and machine-readable format

You also have the right to make a complaint at any time to the Information Commissioner's Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues (www.ico.org.uk). We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with your concerns before you approach the ICO, so please contact us before escalating your complaint.

8\. Marketing
-------------

We will only send you marketing emails about collections, Users and Content we think may be of interest to you.

Wakelet does not send you marketing communications about third-party products or services. Users may display any content, including advertising, so long as it does not conflict with our Code of Conduct.

You can ask us to stop sending you these emails at any time by using the “Unsubscribe” link in each email.

If you do unsubscribe, we will still use your information to present Content on Wakelet, which we think will be of interest to you, but will not send you messages about these.

9\. Information Choices and Changes
-----------------------------------

Registered Users may access or modify the personal information you have provided to us and that is associated with your account at any time. You can log in to Wakelet and visit your account settings page or email us at [admin@wakelet.com](mailto:admin@wakelet.com) to exercise your rights at any time.

We cannot delete your personal information without deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you delete your User Content from Wakelet or request we do so, please note that User Content might have been copied or stored by other users. Please note, if you are part of an Education or Education Pro plan, User Content created by the group is owned by that group and any of these Users can request for the content to be deleted.

If you want to delete your user account, you can do this in your account settings page. Given the sharing, commenting, and dialogue that takes place on Wakelet, some of the public activity on your account prior to deletion may have been copied to third-party servers outside of our control and so may remain accessible to the public indefinitely.

10\. COPPA and Students
-----------------------

General provisions for Children over the age of 13:

You must be over the age of 13 to be a Registered User of Wakelet as part of our Individual or Individual Pro plans.

Children under 13 years of age may only use Wakelet under the supervision of a responsible adult (over the age of 18) who has agreed to our Terms and the provisions in respect of their responsibilities as a 'Group Registered User', as part of an Education or Education Pro plan. We do not send any marketing messages or advertising targeting children under the age of 13. In order to create an account in Wakelet we require every user to verify that they are not under 13 years of age, and we do not permit children under the age of 13 to create an account.

We expect that use by children will only be done with the guidance, supervision and consent of their parents, guardians and/or authorized school officials. Further, we rely on parents and guardians to ensure minors only use the Service if they can understand their rights and responsibilities as stated in our Rules, Terms and this Privacy Policy. We encourage parents to educate their children about safety online and to carefully monitor their children's use of social features to ensure they do not disclose their personal information through them.

We at Wakelet as a data processor are compliant with COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act) and FERPA (Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act). We encourage schools and teachers to be aware of these regulations and not share any Children's or Student's PII outside of a Wakelet Classroom. If Schools prefer to collect parental consent directly from the parent or guardians that is at the Schools or Teachers discretion. Again, please do not disclose or share any Students personal identifiable information. For more information on complying with COPPA, see the Federal Trade Commission's website at [http://www.ftc.gov/privacy.coppafaqs.shtm](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy.coppafaqs.shtm)

If you are outside of the United States, please ensure that you are complying with any laws applicable to you before using Wakelet with students.

If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at [privacy@wakelet.com](mailto:privacy@wakelet.com). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information without verification of parental consent, we will take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account. To protect your privacy and security, we may require you to take certain steps or provide additional information to verify your identity before we provide any information or make corrections.

K-12 Educators:

Children that are under the age of 13 that are associated with an Educational Entity, follow the parental consent process through the policies and procedures established by the Educational Entity.

Prior to a student submitting any information within a School setting by accessing Wakelet's online classroom, the Teacher must certify that he/she received permission and either a) chose to act as an agent of the Parent and consented on Parents behalf under what is commonly referred to under COPPA as school consent or b) collected the appropriate parental consent.

Teachers and the onboarding process for Students in an Educational environment are as follows, as part of our Education and Education Pro plans.

Teachers can invite students under the age of 13 as follows as the Student accounts created as part of the Classrooms feature are private and they have limited features for use in a classroom environment. For example, Students with one of these "private accounts" will, by default, not be able to use certain features embedded in the service that are not suitable for students under 13, including YouTube and Twitter. Students imported in this way cannot publish any content publicly or make any content publicly available. Students in this online classroom environment only share their class work and profiles with other students in the same classroom.

Teachers should ensure that they do not publish information containing Student data within their own collections (which can be made public) without relevant consent.

Process for creating student accounts and Classrooms (legacy users)

The teacher can go to the 'Classrooms' area and import a class of students by using one of the available single sign-on apps.

Once the classroom is imported, the system will create individual student accounts for everyone in the online classroom. The Student can then login using their usual single sign on details. Only the teacher will have the ability to create the Student Account as well as sharing and monitoring any of the content in the online classroom. Teachers will also have the option of removing any of the students or adding new students to the online classroom.

Our Data Handling, including, collection, involves specifically:

* first name and last name
    
* E-Mail address
    
* other student ID
    
* date of birth
    
* school name
    
* teams/clubs
    
* photographs, video or audio file
    
* browser type
    
* access time
    
* time spent on Wakelet App
    
* page views
    
* referring URLS
    
* grade year

Process for creating student accounts and Classrooms (Education and Education Pro users)

All student accounts for these plans will be created through a rostering tool such as Clever or Classlink. Once this data connection has been established with the school or district, students will be set up within secure classroom environments and will be able to log in via the chosen single sign on method.

The school/district administrator will have access to a dashboard view of all of the accounts created and set sharing permissions and integrations by age group as well as view analytics and monitor usage within individual accounts as required.

Should you or your parent have any questions, concerns or requests about these COPPA provisions of this Privacy Policy and are a User or parent of a User of an Educational Entity, you should as a first level of support, contact the administrator at the Educational Entity. If questions, concerns or requests are not addressed by the administrator at the Educational Entity, you or your parent should, as a second level of support, contact us as follows:

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or wish to contact us, please contact [support@wakelet.com](mailto:support@wakelet.com). You can reach Wakelet by post at:

Wakelet Limited  
Bright Building  
Manchester Science Park  
5 Pencroft Way  
Manchester  
M15 6GZ  
United Kingdom

Our data protection manager can be contacted at [DPManager@wakelet.com](mailto:DPManager@wakelet.com)

11\. Spaces (legacy users)
--------------------------

Spaces is an built-in feature of Wakelet accessible to legacy users which provides a streamlined way to organize a collection, Learning Project, Research Project or create any Spaces for the purpose of formulating rich content in an online environment.

A teacher may create Spaces for collaborative activities in the Wakelet Spaces feature. If invited Users are Students, they would be able to create their own collections with the supervision of the Teacher.

Students may be invited to join as a member of a Space by the teacher in one of the two methods described below:

1) The Teacher can provide a link to join by sharing this with the Student through a Student/Parent email account.

2) The Teacher can provide a Spaces Code to the Student/Parent by an in-Class Slip or an Email Account of the Student/Parent.

Once the Student has joined and become a member of the Space, the Teacher will be involved in the creation of the Collections prepared by individual students. Students submissions to the Space will be supervised and approved by the teacher. The Space will be marked as Private by the teacher in the Profile Visibility Setting. Only the Teacher will have the ability to control this setting in the Space.

12\. Rights of California Residents
-----------------------------------

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents have the right to request a list of all third parties to which we have disclosed personal information during the previous year for direct marketing purposes. Wakelet does not share users' personal information with third-party marketers.

If you are a California resident, you can request a list of personal information about you we have disclosed to third parties in the preceding calendar year, as well as the names and address of those third parties. You may make such a request only once per year, and you don't have to pay for it. To make a request, send an email to [support@wakelet.com](mailto:support@wakelet.com) or send a written request to Wakelet, Bright Building, Manchester Science Park, Pencroft Way, Manchester M15 6GZ, UK.

13\. Changes to this Policy
---------------------------

We may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy that we believe will materially affect your rights, we will provide at least 30 days prior notice before any changes take effect, except that we may make changes necessary or advisable to improve security or comply with law without prior notice. If you are a Registered User, we will notify you of these changes via email and/or by asking you to review and acknowledge or accept the changes to this Policy the next time you login to Wakelet. Otherwise, for non-material changes, the Privacy Policy will be updated on the Service. You should consult this Policy regularly for any changes.

14\. Contact Information
------------------------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or wish to contact us, please contact [support@wakelet.com](mailto:support@wakelet.com). You can reach Wakelet by post at:

Wakelet Limited  
Bright Building  
Manchester Science Park  
5 Pencroft Way  
Manchester  
M15 6GZ  
United Kingdom

Our data protection manager can be contacted at [DPManager@wakelet.com](mailto:DPManager@wakelet.com)

Wakelet participates in the iKeepSafe Safe Harbor program. If you have any questions or need to file a complaint related to our privacy policy and practices, please do not hesitate to contact the iKeepSafe Safe Harbor program at [COPPAprivacy@ikeepsafe.org](mailto:COPPAprivacy@ikeepsafe.org).

15\. Definitions
----------------

Here are some definitions of capitalized words we use in these Terms:

"Agents" means service providers, consultants and other third-parties and agents not employed by us.

"Content" means any information, text, graphics, photographs, images, illustrations, logos, tools, written posts, executable files, scripts, software, interactive features, creative expression, data or other information materials generated, provided, uploaded, downloaded, appearing or otherwise accessible on or through Wakelet.

"Interactive Services" means message boards, chat rooms, personal web pages or profiles, forums, bulletin boards and other interactive features.

"Registered User" means a User who has registered and created an account to use Wakelet.

"Service" means Wakelet.com and all other domains, products, applications, services and Content provided by Wakelet.

"Terms" means these terms of agreement between us and you.

"User" means any person or entity using Wakelet.

"You" means you, whether you are a person or someone acting on behalf of an entity you are authorized to represent, and whether you are a Registered User or not.

"User Comments" means any comments, recommends, feedback, likes, or other Content posted by Users that is not included in the body of a Wakelet post.

* Product

* Community

* Company

© Wakelet 2024. All rights reserved
